Worth noting is that this is the year we are growing the top line of the company through the largest LOE period that the company has seen.
Core net financial expense will be one will be around one point seven billion dollars and core tax rate would be about sixteen and a half percent.
And these two parameters are consistent with our previous estimates.
Like twenty two.
Please continue to expect twenty twenty six to be a year of two halves.
Each one growth will be impacted by a tough previous year base following U.S.
generic increase for interest.
So come out and the signal made last year.
And with that in the base, we had guided each one sales to decline low single digit and core operating to decline low double digits with our Q1 results.
Now in the bank, we are on track to meet that guidance.
With Q2 sales expected to decline low single digit and core operating expected to decline high single digit to low double digit.
In half to the impact of the U.S.
Generic entries in the base will start to minimize and this will allow strong growth of our priority brands and launches to show through the overall P&L.
And hence, we continue to expect edge to sales growth of mid single digit and core operating growth of mid to high single digit.
And that brings us to our folio guidance.
Next slide, please.
If exchange rates remain at late April levels, we expect positive plus two percent impact on folio sales and positive one percent on full folio core operating income.
As a reminder, updated exchange rate assumptions are published monthly on our Web site.
And then that concludes my remarks and I'll hand it back to us.
Great.
Thank you, McCool.
And welcome as well, McCool, for his first question.
Thank you so much, and my pleasure.
Thank you all for being here today.
So overall, we've delivered a strong start in 2026 across our priority brands and launches and we remain fully confident with our mid to long term growth outlook.
We continue to advance our pipeline, completed the ability acquisition and are well set up for multiple readouts in the second half.
Remain on track to deliver our folio guidance.
And we'll also look forward to those readouts, which could enable us to raise our mid to long term growth outlook.